Finding Aid for University Planner's Office (University of Michigan) records, 1940-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University Planner's Office (University of Michigan) records 1940-2014
University of Michigan. University Planner's Office.
9571 Bimu 2
The University Planner's Office oversees the master planning, site planning, and site design for the university. The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, architectural drawings, and photographs spanning the years 1840 to 2014.
48 linear feet
1 oversize volume
58.5 GB (online)
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The University Planner's Office (Donor no. 5582 ) makes periodic additions to the records.
The records are open to research.
The University Planner's Office has historically reported to Plant Extension and is an offshoot of the University Architect's Office. The responsibilities of the two offices have often overlapped and their respective responsibilities for campus development and upkeep are intertwined. The office oversees master planning, site planning and site design. The University Planner's Office also manages the review of all exterior element designs including signage, furnishings, public art, and lighting.1
The University Architect's Office was established in 1957 within the Plant Service Department, with Lynn W. Fry the first person to hold the title of University Architect. In 1964 John D. Telfer, formerly the Assistant to the University Architect, became the university's first University Planner. Telfer served in this position until 1968.
As stated above, the responsibilities of the University Planner are tangential to those of the University Architect, both being the natural result of an expanding, growing university community. The University Architect's Office devotes the bulk of its time to advising and serving as liaison between architects and the university community on construction and renovation projects. The role of the University Planner's Office is akin to that of a civil engineer and is concerned with the issues that accompany campus development, including zoning, street construction, signage, landscaping, exterior lighting, and parking.
For further information regarding building projects at the University of Michigan, the researcher should also consult the records of the University Architect's Office.
The records are arranged into four series: Campus Development and History, Master Planning, Properties, and Projects.
The records of the University Planner's Office consist of 48 linear feet, 72.3 GB of digital files, and one oversize volume. Records contain correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, architectural drawings, and photographs spanning the years 1840 to 2014. The records document the role of the University Planner's Office in campus planning on the University of Michigan campuses and in conjunction with the City of Ann Arbor.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. University Planner's Office.; Construction industry--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Architecture--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan--Buildings.; Landscape architecture.; University of Michigan--Campus.; University of Michigan--Parking.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
University of Michigan. University Planner's Office.; University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan--Campus.
Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Digital file formats.; Photographs.
- Campus Development and History, 1840-2008
  The Campus Development and History series (1840-2008, 3 linear feet and 17 GB) is divided into two subseries: Early Campus Development and Campus History.
  - Early Campus Development, 1840-2011, 1840-1925
    Early Campus Development contains information regarding early campus landscaping, old plans, and various reports from the early 20th century.
    - Campus Plans and Landscaping, 1840-1955 (Box 9)
    - Old Plans, The Univ. of Michigan Ann Arbor, 1840-1966 (Box 9)
    - Campus Plan, 1907-1908 (Box 9)
    - Olmsted Brothers, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Olmsted Report, 1922 (Box 9)
    - Comprehensive Building Program, 1921 (Box 9)
    - Committee of Five Minutes, 1921-1925 (Box 9)
    - President's Reports, 1920-1925 (Box 9)
    - Reports, 1920-1923 (Box 9)
    - Pitkin and Mott, 1919-1943 (Box 9)
    - Residence Halls, 1911-2001 (Box 9)
  - Campus History, 1840-2008 (Box 10)
    The Campus History subseries contains compiled research from 1840 to the early 2000s. Included are clippings, Public Works Program documentation, old walking tours, photographs and slides.
    - UM History-General
      - Pre-1840 (Box 10)
      - 1840-1849 (Box 10)
      - 1850-1859 (Box 10)
      - 1860-1869 (Box 10)
      - 1870-1879 (Box 10)
      - 1880-1889 (Box 10)
      - 1890-1899 (Box 10)
      - 1900-1909 (Box 10)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 10)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 10)
      - 1930-939 (Box 10)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 10)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 10)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 10)
      - National Register Central Campus, 1975-1978 (Box 10)
    - Constitutional and Legislative Acts, Legal Decisions, and By-Laws of the University of Michigan, 1923 (Box 10)
    - UM Buildings-General
      - Pre-1860 (Box 10)
      - 1880-1900 (Box 10)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 10)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 10)
      - 1960-1979 (Box 10)
      - Alumnus Articles, 1920s (Box 10)
    - Deed 1-Original 40 Acres (Box 10)
    - Underground Railroad, 1998-2002 (Box 10)
    - World's Columbian Expo, 1893 (Box 10)
    - Post War Public Works Program, 1943 (Box 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1954-1959 (Box 10)
    - Brochures and Walking Tours, 1895-2010
      - Records (Box 11)
      - Digital records
    - Copyrights, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Building Information Chronological Development, 1987-2014 (Box 11)
    - Student Housing and Enrollment, 1950-1996 (Box 11)
    - Ann Arbor Historic Districts and Properties, 1979-2008 (Box 11)
    - Campus Infrastructure, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Campus Furniture, 1979 (Box 11)
    - The Implementable Plan, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Campus Street Names, 1963-2006 (Box 11)
    - 20 year Employee Service Awards, 2004 (Box 11)
    - M1 Data Entry-November, 1952 (Box 11)
    - Aerial Photographs, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Huron Valley Photos, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Ann Arbor Areas and Buildings Slides, undated (Box 11)
    - The University of Michigan Statistical Reference Book, 1965 (Box 12)
    - School of Children's Dentistry, P.W.A. Project, 1938-1940 (Box 12)
    - Dormitory for Women, Observatory St. and N. Univ. Ave., P.W.A. Project, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
    - Internes Quarters Project, 1939 (Box 12)
    - Men's Dormitory, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
    - Medical Students Dormitory, Catherine Street Project, 1939 (Box 12)
    - Heating Plant Installation, 1939 (Box 12)
    - Campus Photographs, 1950-2008 (Box 12)
    - Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1997-2008 (Box 12)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital, undated (Box 12)
    - Mid-1980s Downtown Aerial, undated (Box 12)
    - Campus Negatives, undated (Box 12)
- Master Planning, 1950-2009
  The Master Planning series (1950-2009, 8.5 linear feet) is separated into five subseries: Central Campus, East Medical Campus, North Campus, Dearborn Campus, and Flint campus. The series, and each subseries, contains materials relating to the master plans of each campus, research reports, correspondence, land deeds, and photographs and slides of buildings and lands.
  - Central Campus
    - Planning
      - 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 13)
    - Plan Concept, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Traffic and Parking Analysis, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Photographs, 1965-1982 (Box 13)
    - Planning Study
      - 1963 (Box 49)
      - 1987 (Box 49)
    - Planning Projects in Central Campus Plan, 1982-1989 (Box 13)
    - Central Campus Redevelopment, 1960 (Box 42)
    - Site Study, 1971 (Box 42)
    - Building Site Inventory, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Changes in Central Campus Land Use 1964-1996, 1996 (Box 42)
    - The University of Michigan Campus Walkways, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Campus Tree Concept, 1962 (Box 42)
    - Buildings Under Study
      - 1962 (Box 42)
      - 1963 (Box 42)
      - 1965 (Box 42)
      - 1967 (Box 42)
      - 1976 (Box 42)
    - Slides
      - Building Photos, 1956-2002, 11 folders (Box 46)
      - General Areas, 1956-2002, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - Aerials, 1956-2002, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Maps, Plans, and Models, 1956-2002, 3 folders (Box 46)
  - East Medical Campus
    - Medical Center Photographs, 1950-1983 (Box 13)
    - Master Plan, 1994-1998 (Box 13)
    - Planning, undated (Box 13)
    - Medical Center Planning Report, 1961, 2 volumes (Box 42)
    - Open Space Study, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Physical Facilities Planning Guide, 1961-1967 (Box 42)
    - Capacity Study, 1991 (Box 42)
    - Parking Study, 1995 (Box 42)
    - Slides, 1961-2000, 6 folders (Box 46)
  - South Campus
    - Projects in Stadium Area, 1988-1992 (Box 13)
    - Planning Study, 1991 (Box 49)
    - Slides, 1947-2002, 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens and Radrick Farms
    - Photographs, 1994, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Planning, 1983-1999 (Box 13)
  - North Campus
    - History, 1959-2014 (Box 14)
    - Planning, 1949-1977, 11 folders (Box 14)
    - Streets, 1960-1962 (Box 14)
    - Tracings, 1961-1973 (Box 14)
    - Married Student Housing, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Affiliated Housing and Fraternity Report, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Land Analysis, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Environmental Report, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
    - "Environmental Survey", 1977 (Box 14)
    - Items Transferred to Bentley, 2009 (Box 14)
    - Deed Research, 1952-1987 (Box 15)
    - Goss Property Site Analysis, 1969-1980 (Box 15)
    - North Campus Planning Study, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Environmental Survey, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Master Landscape Plan, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Slides, 1957-2002, 8 folders (Box 48)
  - Dearborn Campus
    - General information, 1958-1974, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Long Range Development Plan UM-D, 1973 (Box 15)
      - Summary Report (Box 15)
      - Detailed Report (Box 15)
    - Campus Development Plan
      - April Printing, 1990 (Box 15)
      - December Printing, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Fair Lane
      - Documents and Research, 1973-2008 (Box 15)
      - Booklet, 1974 (Box 15)
      - Centennial booklet, 1963 (Box 49)
    - Slides, undated (Box 15)
  - Flint Campus
    - Plan, 1970-2003 (Box 16)
    - Campus Plan Study, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Flint North Bank Center, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Feasibility Study, 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Assembling a River Front Site, 1972, 2 volumes (Box 16)
    - Slides, 1957-2002 (Box 16)
    - General, 1964-1986, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Reports
      - "Campus Development Plan" (Johnson, Johnson & Roy)
        - Volume One
          - "General Plan," 1973 (Box 3)
          - "Technical Appendix," undated (Box 3)
        - Volume Three: "Plan Evaluation and Phasing Refinement," 1974 (Box 3)
        - Volume Four: "Plan Refinement and Update," 1983 (Box 3)
      - "Court Street Property Study: Land Use Feasibility Analysis," 1981 (Box 3)
      - "Site Investigation, Riverfront Site Proposal, University of Michigan-Flint" (Sasaki Dawson DeMay Associates), 1972 (Box 3)
      - "Specifications for Separate Contracts, Site Construction Work and Site Landscape Work, 1981 Campus Site Improvements at the University of Michigan-Flint Riverfront Site" (Johnson, Johnson & Roy), 1981 (Box 3)
      - "Subsoil Investigation and Foundation Feasibility Study, Final Report" (Raymond C. Reese Associates), 1972 (Box 3)
      - "Traffic Impact Study: Riverfront Site, University of Michigan-Flint" (Wilbur Smith and Associates), 1973 (Box 3)
      - "The University of Michigan Flint Campus Plan Study" (Beckett Jackson Raeder Inc.; Samborn, Steketee, Otis and Evans, Inc.), 1971, 2 volumes (Box 3)
- Properties, 1850-2014
  The Properties series (1850-2014, 24 linear feet and 41.5 GB) is divided into five subseries: Buildings by Number, Buildings by Name, Removed Buildings, Miscellaneous Properties, and Public Art. Buildings by Number, Removed Buildings, and Miscellaneous Properties are organized by differing numbering systems used by the University's Planner's Office. Each property's folder contains a historical report containing information regarding construction and press releases. Deed and gift records, photographs, slides, management, and rights information can also be found within these files.
  - Buildings by number
    - 0005 Nichols Arlo Residence and 0010 Burnham House, 1990-2007 (Box 17)
    - 0040-0047 Oxford Housing, 1972-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0051 Betsy Barbour Residence, 2008-2010
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0052-Martha Cook Residence, 1997-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0053 Couzens Hall 1995-2009
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0054 East Quad, 1967-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0055 Fletcher Hall, 2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0057 Henderson Hall, 1994-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0059 Alice Lloyd Hall, 2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0060 Mary Markley Hall, 1955-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0061 Mosher-Jordan Hall, 1997-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0062 Helen Newberry Residence, 2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0063 South Quad, 1997-2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0064 Stockwell Hall, 2008
      - Records (Box 17)
      - Digital records
    - 0065 Victor Vaughan House, 2008
      - Records (Box 18)
      - Digital records
    - 0066 West Quad, undated
      - Records (Box 18)
      - Digital records
    - 0100 Mental Health Research, undated (Box 18)
    - 0105 Student Publications Building, 2008
      - Records (Box 18)
      - Digital records
    - 0108 Law Quad, undated, 7 folders (Box 18)
    - 0120 Michigan Union, 2008
      - Records, 7 folders (Box 18)
      - Digital records
    - 0137 Kresge Business Administration Library, 1979-1987 (Box 19)
    - 0139 Business Administration Executive Dorm, 1984 (Box 19)
    - 0145 Institute for Social Research, 1965-2009
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Digital records
    - 0149 Fleming Robben and Aldyth Administration Building, 1964-2010
      - Records (Box 19)
      - Digital records
    - 0150 Literature, Science, and the Arts Building, 1949-2008
      - Records, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Digital records
    - 0151 Alumni Memorial Hall, 1946-2009
      - Records, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Digital records
    - 0152 Angell Hall, 0175 Haven Hall, 0197 Mason Hall, 0206 Angell Hall Auditoriums, 1967-2008
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Digital records
    - 0154 Lorch Hall, 1965-2008
      - Records (Box 20)
      - Digital records
    - 0155 Burton Tower, 1936-2008 (Box 20)
    - 0158 Chemistry Building and Dow Lab, 1956-2008
      - Records, 8 folders (Box 20)
      - Digital records
    - 0159 Clements Library, 1965-2008
      - Records (Box 20)
      - Digital records
    - 0162 Kellogg Institute and Dental Building, 1963-2010
      - Records (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0165 Dennison Building, 1961-2009
      - Records (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0166 East Engineering, 1958-2008
      - Records (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0167 West Engineering, 1958-2008
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0172 Rackham Graduate School, 1942-2008
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0176 Health Service, 1942-2008
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Digital records
    - 0177 Hill Auditorium
      - 1958-2002, 5 folders
      - 1958-2002, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - 0178 Newberry Hall/Kelsey Museum, 1989-2009
      - Records, 7 folders (Box 22)
      - Digital records
    - 0180 Power Center for the Performing Arts, 1964-1980 (Additional Publications (Box 23)
    - 0183 Lane Hall, 1998-2006
      - Records (Box 23)
      - Digital records
    - 0185 and 0181 Hatcher Graduate Library, 1956-2012
      - Records, 4 folders (Box 23)
      - Digital records
    - 0186 Pound House, 1975-1999 (Box 23)
    - 0188 C. C. Little (East Medical), 1969-2010
      - Records (Box 23)
      - Digital records
    - 0189 Dana (West Medical), 1974-2010
      - Records (Box 23)
      - Digital records
    - 0190/0200 Medical Sciences, 1955-2010
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Digital records
    - 0191 Michigan League, 1946-2004
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Digital records
    - 0192 Alumni Center, 1966-1983 (Box 24)
    - 0193 Ruthven Museum, 1964-2004
      - Records (Box 24)
      - Digital records
    - 0194 Museums Annex, 2008
      - Records (Box 24)
      - Digital records
    - 0196 North Hall, 2005-2008
      - Records (Box 24)
      - Digital records
    - 0198 Detroit Observatory, 1974-2004
      - Records, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - 0201 Hartwig Administration Building, 1983-2008
      - Records (Box 24)
      - Digital records
    - 0203 Presidents House, 1887-2007
      - Records, 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Digital records
    - 0204 Henry Vaughan Public Health Building, 1955-2011
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Digital records
    - 0205 Psychological Clinic/1027 East Huron Building, 1995 (Box 25)
    - 0207 Modern Language Building, 1965-2002 (Box 25)
    - 0208 Randall Lab, 1982-2010
      - Records (Box 25)
      - Digital records
    - 0209 Taubman Medical Library, 1975-2010, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - 0210 Buhl Research Center for Human Genetics, 1964 (Box 26)
    - 0211 Edward Henry Kraus Building, 1968-2011
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Digital records
    - 0212 Simpson Memorial Institute, 1977-2010
      - Records (Box 26)
      - Digital records
    - 0214 1007 East Huron (Whitman House) 1976-1995 (Box 26)
    - 0215 Student Activities Building, 1955-2006 (Box 26)
    - 0216 Tappan Hall, 1969-2006
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Digital records
    - 0221 School of Education, 1969-2013
      - Records (Box 27)
      - Digital records
    - 0222 News and Information Services Building, 1955-2014 (Box 27)
    - 0225 Dance Building, 1975-1978 (Box 27)
    - 0226 Central Campus Recreation Building and Margaret Bell Pool, 1969-2011
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Digital records
    - 0227 Harold and Vivian Shapiro Library, 1956-2008 (Box 27)
    - 0230 College of Pharmacy, 1959-1990 (Box 27)
    - 0253 Hill Street Parking Structure, 1967-1969 (Box 27)
    - 0254 Fletcher Street Parking Structure, 1969-1988 (Box 27)
    - 0255 Thompson Street Parking Structure, 1970-2009 (Box 27)
    - 0257 Church Street Parking Structure, 1971-1988 (Box 27)
    - 0258 Catherine Street Parking Structure, 1985 (Box 27)
    - 0259 Thayer Street Parking Structure, 1985 (Box 27)
    - 0260 Central Power Plant, 1956-2005 (Box 27)
    - 0308 Med Inn, 1963-1983 (Box 27)
    - 0309 Women's Hospital, 1968-2014 (Box 27)
    - 0312 C. S. Mott Children's Hospital, 1964-2014 (Box 27)
    - 0313 Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education, 1966-2011
      - Records (Box 27)
      - Digital records
    - 0314 Holden Perinatal Research Lab, 1977-2014 (Box 27)
    - 0319 Medical Professional Building, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
    - 0324 Kellogg Eye Center, 1979-2006 (Box 27)
    - 0332 North Ingalls Building, 1969-1981 (Box 27)
    - 0333 School of Nursing Building, 1973-1990, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - 0400 Walter E. Lay Automotive Engineering Laboratory, 1956-2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0402 Bonisteel Interdisciplinary Research Building, 1954-2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0403 Mortimer E Cooley, 1955-2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0404 Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project, 1961-2013
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0405 Ford Nuclear Reactor, 1974-2013
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0406 Ann and Robert H. Lurie Biomedical Engineering Building, 2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0407 George Granger Brown Memorial Laboratories, 1982-2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0414 Environmental and Water Resources Engineering Building, 1966-1993, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - 0415 Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering Building, 1977-2007 (Box 28)
    - 0416 and 0417 Engineering Radiation Laboratory, 2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0419 Laundry Building, 1968-1969 (Box 28)
    - 0420 Computing Center, 1966-1985 (Box 28)
    - 0421-0426 Aerospace Engineering Laboratories, 2007
      - Records (Box 28)
      - Digital records
    - 0424 Engineering Programs Building, 1972 (Box 28)
    - 0427 North Campus Recreation Building, 1973-1974 (Box 28)
    - 0429 Industrial and Operations Engineering Building, 1961-2007
      - Records (Box 29)
      - Digital records
    - 0432 Art and Architecture, 1965-2004, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - 0433-0437 Institute of Science and Technology, 1960-2007
      - Records (Box 29)
      - Digital records
    - 0439 Bentley Historical Library, 1969-2010, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 0440 Earl V. Moore Building, 1962-2007
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Digital records
    - 0441 Space Research Building, 1974-2007
      - Records (Box 29)
      - Digital records
    - 0442 Pierpont Commons, 1973-2013
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Digital records
    - 0443 Chrysler Center, 1965-1968 (Box 30)
    - 0444 Transportation Research Institute/Highway Safety Research Institute, 1965-1990, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - 0445 Stearns Building, 1973-1996 (Box 30)
    - 0446 Gerald R Ford Library, 1977-2007 (Box 30)
    - 0447 Herbert H. Dow Building, 1979-1998, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - 0450-0508, 0601-0683, 2701-2779 Northwood Apartments, 1968-2011 (Box 30)
    - 0510-0519 Vera Baits Housing, 1964-2012
      - Records (Box 30)
      - Digital records
    - 0555 Bursley Hall, 1964-2008
      - Records (Box 30)
      - Digital records
    - 0700 Crisler Arena, 1964-2012 (Box 30)
    - 0703 Track and Tennis Building, 1973 (Box 30)
    - 0704 Bennie Oosterbaan Field House, 1980 (Box 30)
    - 0705 Glenn E. Schembechler Hall, 1988-2006 (Box 30)
    - 0709 Yost Field House Ice Arena, 1973-2007
      - Records (Box 30)
      - Digital records
    - 0710 Coliseum, 1983-2008
      - Records (Box 31)
      - Digital records
    - 0711 Michigan Stadium, 1926-2010, 6 folders (Box 31)
    - 0719 Intramural Building, 1973-2007 (Box 31)
    - 0725 Golf Course and Clubhouse, 1982-2008
      - Records (Box 31)
      - Digital records
    - 0728 Elbel Field and Buildings, 1977-2011 (Box 31)
    - 0731 Weidenbach Hall, 2006-2008
      - Records (Box 31)
      - Digital records
    - 0732 Cliff Keen Arena, 1955-2007
      - Records (Box 31)
      - Digital records
    - 0733 Fisher Baseball Stadium, 2005-2008 (Box 31)
    - 0742 Campus Safety Services, 1971-1994 (Box 31)
    - 0799 Buhr Building, 1972-1996 (Box 31)
    - 0800-0808 Hoover Ave Plant Complex, 1956-2006, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 0811-0812 University Chemical and Food Stores, 1968-2009, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 0813 Revelli Hall, 1977-1994 (Box 31)
    - 0814 Institute of Continuing Legal Education, 1984-1987 (Box 32)
    - 0815 Administrative Services, 1961-1979 (Box 32)
    - 0816 Mail Service, 1975 (Box 32)
    - 0829 Wilmot House, 1977 (Box 32)
    - 0831 Argus II, 1970-2000 (Box 32)
    - 0851 Observatory Lodge, 2005-2008 (Box 32)
    - 0853 Ferdon, 1979-2012 (Box 32)
    - 0857 Oxford, 2013 (Box 32)
    - 0858 Madison Building, 1975-2000 (Box 32)
    - 0861 Inglis House, 1952-2007 (Box 32)
    - 0883 Nu Sigma Nu, 1966-2004 (Box 32)
    - 0886 Trotter house, 1977-2013
      - Records (Box 32)